<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LRMI Home Page on LRMI</title>
    <link>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LRMI Home Page on LRMI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 17:57:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://lrmi.dublincore.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LRMI Concept Schemes</title>
      <link>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/concept_schemes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/concept_schemes/</guid>
      <description>DCMI Home&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; LRMI 1.1&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Return to Community Specifications TOC
   Creator: LRMI Task Group (DC-Education Community)     Editors: Phil Barker and Stuart Sutton   Identifier: @@@   Current Version: @@@   Previous Version: &amp;ndash;   Date Issued: 2018-01-15   Document Status: Community Specification   Description: The LRMI concept schemes are small sets of concepts for use as values with the LRMI properties in learning resource description and Web markup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/about/</guid>
      <description>LRMI Today—2014 to Present Effective 23 October 2014, the LRMI 1.1 specification was transferred to the Dublin Core Metadata Initiatve (DCMI). A full description of the terms of the transfer is available. The responsibility of stewardship and the further development of the LRMI specification belongs to a new permanent LRMI Task Group (TG) as an adjunct to DCMI’s long-standing Education Community. The work of the TG is advanced through the definition of specific work packages with specific tasks, goals, and timeframes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Announcement</title>
      <link>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/transfer_announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 17:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://lrmi.dublincore.org/transfer_announcement/</guid>
      <description>LRMI Transfers Stewardship Effective October 23, 2014, leadership and governance of the Learning Resource Metadata Initiative (LRMI), an education metadata project developed to improve discoverability and delivery of learning resources, have transferred from the Association of Educational Publishers and Creative Commons to the Dublin Core Metadata Initiative (DCMI).
This long-planned transfer represents a logical next step for the LRMI since the project has reached the end of its initial scope of work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>